♪I lament on the cruel and untimely love♪
أنا أتحسر على الحب القاسي والغير أوانه ♪
♪Yet I come to realise it's a daydream when the bubbles burst♪
♪ ومع ذلك أدركت أنه حلم يقظة عندما تنفجر الفقاعات ♪
♪A city of spring flowers♪
♪ مدينة زهور الربيع ♪
♪Sinks into the indifferent autumnal frost♪
♪ يغرق في الصقيع الخريفي غير المبال
♪A snowflake falls into the river♪
♪ تسقط ندفة ثلجية في النهر ♪
♪The biting cold stalks over♪
♪ البرد القارص ينبع
♪All assumptions are nothing♪
كل الافتراضات لا شيء
♪But a disguised makeup♪
♪ لكن مكياج مقنع
♪I bid farewell♪
أودع
♪To the passionate gaze behind the mask♪
♪ للنظرة العاطفية خلف القناع ♪
♪Love and hate are the most unforgettable feelings♪
الحب والكراهية من أكثر المشاعر التي لا تنسى
♪Overwhelmed by my longings♪
غارقة في شوقي ♪
♪I tear off those old scores♪
♪ مزقت تلك الدرجات القديمة ♪
♪I bid farewell♪
أودع
♪To the irretrievable past♪
إلى الماضي الذي لا يمكن استرجاعه ♪
=Little Mad Doctor=
= الطبيب المجنون الصغير =
=Episode 15=
= الحلقة 15 =
Please forgive me.
رجائاً أعطني.
I'm to blame.
انا الملام.
My Lord, please.
ربي من فضلك.
I didn't mean to do that.
لم أقصد أن أفعل ذلك.
This is my first time
هذه المرة الأولى بالنسبة لي
carrying a girl.
تحمل فتاة.
I was kind of nervous.
كنت متوترة نوعا ما.
Please forgive me.
رجائاً أعطني.
Make sure there's no next time.
تأكد من عدم وجود المرة القادمة.
Ah! I don't have the guts for that again.
آه!  ليس لدي الشجاعة لذلك مرة أخرى.
She's deeply sensitive
إنها حساسة للغاية
to discern
أن نستشف
such details.
مثل هذه التفاصيل.
That's right.
صحيح.
Princess Jinghong is too good at acting cute.
الأميرة جينغهونغ جيدة جدا في التمثيل اللطيف.
I can't resist.
لا استطيع المقاومة.
Did she act cute towards you?
هل تصرفت بلطف تجاهك؟
No, not to me.
لا ، ليس لي.
To you.
لك.
Ah, it's me.
آه ، هذا أنا.
No, she was doing that to me who's wearing your face.
لا ، لقد كانت تفعل ذلك بي أنا الذي يرتدي وجهك.
Wushuang.
وشوانغ.
I said no to Ming Bao'er just now.
لقد قلت لا لـ Ming Bao'er الآن.
Please keep an eye on her
من فضلك راقبها
to keep her in check.
لإبقائها تحت السيطرة.
I won't meet her for the time being.
لن أقابلها في الوقت الحالي.
But
لكن
it's not a good choice
إنه ليس اختيارًا جيدًا
to confine Ming Bao'er, right?
لحصر مينغ باوير ، أليس كذلك؟
I just want to protect
أنا فقط أريد أن أحمي
the last descendant of the Ming family.
آخر سليل لعائلة مينغ.
Alas.
واحسرتاه.
Did Feibai ask you to come?
هل طلب منك Feibai أن تأتي؟
Yes.
نعم.
Please go back.
من فضلك ارجع.
I don't need you here.
لا أحتاجك هنا.
I said you should leave.
قلت يجب أن تغادر.
Just now, I came under His Highness's order.
الآن فقط ، جئت بأمر من سموه.
But for now,
لكن الان،
I come here myself.
جئت إلى هنا بنفسي.
I'm here as Wushuang.
أنا هنا بصفتي Wushuang.
Are you men all heartless?
هل كلكم رجال بلا قلب؟
No, I'm not like this.
لا ، أنا لست كذلك.
(Perhaps I'm kind of jumpy now.)
(ربما أنا نوع من القفز الآن.)
(This thought is just ridiculous.)
(هذا الفكر سخيف فقط.)
Thanks to your plan,
بفضل خطتك ،
we got to capture the culprit.
علينا القبض على الجاني.
You will have to take over.
سوف تضطر إلى تولي الأمر.
I will pry the answer out
سوف أقوم بإخراج الجواب
of those who are brought
من الذين تم إحضارهم
to the Internal Activities Depot.
إلى مستودع الأنشطة الداخلية.
Oh, right.
صحيح.
Please get that truth out
من فضلك اخرج هذه الحقيقة
before the birthday banquet
قبل مأدبة عيد الميلاد
of the empress.
من الامبراطورة.
No worries.
لا شكر على واجب.
Why do you ask for me?
لماذا تسأل عني؟
Tomorrow
غداً
is the birthday banquet of the empress.
هي وليمة عيد ميلاد الإمبراطورة.
You're going to present the gift
ستقدم الهدية
together with the delegations of Northern Chu.
مع وفود شمال تشو.
I've prepared the gift.
لقد أعددت الهدية.
This is the envoy
هذا هو المبعوث
representing Northern Chu.
تمثل شمال تشو.
She will present the gift together with you.
ستقدم الهدية معك.
Just call her Guo.
فقط اتصل بها قوه.
Is this the gift?
هل هذه الهدية؟
What's this?
ما هذا؟
I'm going to unveil it.
سأقوم بالكشف عنه.
Huh?
هاه؟
Seriously?
بجد؟
A plant?
نبتة؟
Oh.
أوه.
I get it.
أحصل عليه.
Father tries
الأب يحاول
to hint to Emperor Zhaowu
للتلميح إلى الإمبراطور Zhaowu
that he's been cheated by the empress.
أنه تعرض للغش من قبل الإمبراطورة.
Gosh, shut up.
يا الهي ، اخرس.
This is the Queen of the Night with 99 blooms.
هذه هي ملكة الليل مع 99 زهرة.
The Queen of the Night with 99 blooms?
ملكة الليل مع 99 زهرة؟
This is what it looks like?
هذا ما يبدو عليه؟
The birthday present
هدية عيد الميلاد
must be extraordinary.
يجب أن يكون غير عادي.
I made the potion with my blood.
لقد صنعت الجرعة بدمي.
The moment you pour it into the soil,
لحظة صبها في التربة ،
the Queen of the Night will bloom right away.
سوف تتفتح ملكة الليل على الفور.
It must be astonishing.
يجب أن يكون مذهلاً.
There's also a legend about this plant.
هناك أيضًا أسطورة حول هذا النبات.
We shall present it to the empress.
سنقدمها إلى الإمبراطورة.
(Lord War's Residence)
(مقر اللورد وورز)
Tonight, you're attending with the delegations of Northern Chu.
الليلة ، ستحضر مع وفود شمال تشو.
I will dispatch my men to follow you.
سأرسل رجالي لمتابعتك.
Everything will be fine on my side.
كل شيء سيكون على ما يرام من جانبي.
But I'm worried about you.
لكنني قلق عليك.
Your Blood Curse will relapse tonight.
لعنة دمك ستنتكس الليلة.
The banquet
مأدبة
ends at the hour of Hai
ينتهي في ساعة هاي
and it relapses two hours later.
وينتكس بعد ساعتين.
It will be no problem.
لن تكون هناك مشكلة.
My Lord.
ربي.
Delegations of Northern Chu came to fetch Princess Jinghong.
جاءت وفود شمال تشو لجلب الأميرة جينغهونغ.
All right.
حسنًا.
I will get going.
سأذهب.
Guo.
قوه.
Is the potion with you?
هل الدواء معك؟
Make sure everything proceeds as planned.
تأكد من أن كل شيء يسير كما هو مخطط له.
Rest assured, Your Highness.
اطمئن يا صاحب السمو.
Losing this potion is like risking my neck.
فقدان هذه الجرعة مثل المخاطرة برقبتي.
I've practised this many times.
لقد مارست هذا مرات عديدة.
No one will see me when I pour the potion.
لن يراني أحد عندما أسكب الجرعة.
Very good.
جيد جدًا.
At ease.
في سهولة.
Today is the birthday banquet of the empress.
اليوم هو عيد ميلاد الإمبراطورة.
Please drop the honorifics
يرجى ترك الشرف
and make yourself comfortable.
واجعل نفسك مرتاحًا.
-Thank you, Your Majesty.
-شكرا جلالة الملك.  -شكرا جلالة الملك.
(Where's Yu Longyuan?)
(أين يو لونجيوان؟)
Here comes Lord War.
هنا تأتي حرب اللورد.
Greetings,
تحيات،
Your Majesties.
أصحاب الجلالة.
Take your seat.
خذ مقعدك.
(Oh, he's wearing that.)
(أوه ، إنه يرتدي ذلك.)
Longyuan.
لونجيوان.
Look at you.
انظر لحالك.
You're always late.
أنت دائما متأخر.
You ought to take the liquor thrice.
يجب أن تأخذ الخمور ثلاث مرات.
Don't turn it down.
لا ترفضها.
Yes,
نعم،
I will drink.
انا سوف اشرب.
(Do you like)
(هل تحب)
(my outfit?)
(ملابسي؟)
(Yes.)
(نعم.)
The monarch of Dongxia deliberately sought
سعى ملك Dongxia عمدا
this natural pearl from the depths of the East Sea.
هذه اللؤلؤة الطبيعية من أعماق البحر الشرقي.
I wish you many happy returns, Your Majesty.
أتمنى لك كل خير ، جلالة الملك.
The pearls are huge.
اللآلئ ضخمة.
This is peculiar, Your Majesty.
هذا غريب يا جلالة الملك.
The emperor of Dongxia
إمبراطور Dongxia
is so considerate.
مراعي جدا.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
شكرا لك جلالة الملك.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I present you the gift from Northern Chu,
أقدم لك هدية من نورثرن تشو ،
specially prepared
أعدت خصيصا
by my father and brother, Your Majesty.
من والدي وأخي ، جلالة الملك.
This present
هذه الهدية
only listens to you.
يستمع إليك فقط.
Oh?
أوه؟
Chu Jinghong.
تشو جينغهونغ.
Is Northern Chu a poor state?
هل شمال تشو دولة فقيرة؟
Presenting a plant as a birthday gift?
تقديم نبات كهدية عيد ميلاد؟
♪I sigh at my life♪
♪ أنا أتنهد في حياتي ♪
♪There's nowhere to anchor on shore♪
♪ لا يوجد مكان للرسو على الشاطئ
♪Nothing to cherish in the world♪
لا شيء نعتز به في العالم
♪Except for you♪
ما عداك ♪
♪The past we've been through retains♪
♪ الماضي الذي مررنا به
♪Even though time wears thin♪
على الرغم من أن الوقت يضعف ♪
♪The thought of being together lifelong♪
فكرة البقاء معًا مدى الحياة
♪Exists beyond time♪
موجود خارج الزمن ♪
♪All joys and sorrows♪
♪ كل افراح و احزان ♪
♪Reflect in your gentle gaze♪
انعكس في نظراتك اللطيفة
♪I will spend my life waiting♪
♪ سأقضي حياتي في الانتظار ♪
♪For the chance to be forever by your side♪
للحصول على فرصة أن تكون بجانبك إلى الأبد
♪Hair turns grey in one winter night♪
♪ يتحول لون الشعر إلى اللون الرمادي في ليلة شتاء ♪
♪The appearance remains in spite of the thick frost♪
المظهر يبقى بالرغم من الصقيع الكثيف
♪Time slips by in that dream-like world♪
♪ الوقت يمر في هذا العالم الذي يشبه الحلم
♪Life is always full of splendor♪
♪ الحياة دائما مليئة بالروعة
♪We part when the flowers fall♪
♪ نفترق عندما تسقط الأزهار
♪Desolate chills blow away several autumns♪
♪ قشعريرة مقفرة تهب عدة خريفات ♪
♪Eternal love is all I seek♪
الحب الأبدي هو كل ما أسعى إليه
♪Though the sweet dream fades at last♪
رغم أن الحلم الجميل يتلاشى أخيرًا ♪
♪I sigh at my life♪
♪ أنا أتنهد في حياتي ♪
♪There's nowhere to anchor on shore♪
♪ لا يوجد مكان للرسو على الشاطئ
♪Nothing to cherish in the world♪
لا شيء نعتز به في العالم
♪Except for you♪
ما عداك ♪
♪The past we've been through retains♪
♪ الماضي الذي مررنا به
♪Even though time wears thin♪
على الرغم من أن الوقت يضعف ♪
♪The thought of being together lifelong♪
فكرة البقاء معًا مدى الحياة
♪Exists beyond time♪
موجود خارج الزمن ♪
♪All joys and sorrows♪
♪ كل افراح و احزان ♪
♪Reflect in your gentle gaze♪
انعكس في نظراتك اللطيفة
♪I will spend my life waiting♪
♪ سأقضي حياتي في الانتظار ♪
♪For the chance to be forever by your side♪
للحصول على فرصة أن تكون بجانبك إلى الأبد